

BENJAMIN SOLT

FULL STACK ENGINEER

SUMMARY

Full Stack Engineer who is eager to grow and solve new problems.

Past experience in freelance logo, art design, and 3D art/animation and 10 years in retail, developing skills in teamwork, communication, and customer service.

Took initiative to self teach Epic Game's Unreal Engine.

SKILLS

- CSS
- SASS
- HTML
- SQL
- JavaScript
- Git/GitHub
- React
- Node.js
- Redux
- Adobe Creative Suite
- Python
- Unreal Engine
- 3D Studio Max

EDUCATION

LAMBDA SCHOOL - REMOTE

July 2019 - August 2020 Full Stack Web Developer

TEMPLE UNIVERSITY - AMBLER, PA CERTIFICATION IN WEBSITE DESIGN

May 2012

- Intensive course focused on creative web design
- Page layouts and art assets
- Utilized HTML, CSS, and Dreamweaver

THE ART INSTITUTE OF PHILADELPHIA

December 2007

• Bachelor of Science Degree in Media Arts and Animation

CONTACT INFO

- Bensolt@gmail.com
- Cell: 215 360 5410
- Fort Washington, PA
- Bensolt.com
- <u>LinkedIn</u>
- Github

PROJECTS

PORTFOLIO

APRIL 2020 - PRESENT

Built to showcase personal projects HTML | CSS | JavaScript | React

 Designed, developed and implemented React based site to display a diverse range of personal projects

GROA - FRONT END DEVELOPER

FEBRUARY 2020

Built to recommend movies to user, based on how user rates movies HTML | CSS | JavaScript | React | AWS

- As Front End Developer built Authorization, Login, display layout of movie info
- Solved problems and trouble shot bugs with team members
- Collaborated remotely with team of 6 web developers, 2 data science, and 1 UX designer

REACT-REDUX-APP2

DECEMBER 2019

Built to demonstrate API call and Redux HTML | CSS | JavaScript | React | Halo API

- Implemented Halo API database to visualize data from site
- Built a filter to allow a user to search by name of player

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

LOGO AND ART ASSET DESIGNER

WILLOW GROVE, PA

NOVEMBER 2013 - PRESENT

- Created logos and t-shirt graphics, to meet various companies contracted needs
- Designed art assets to display instructional steps and enable end users to envision system process
- Animated, modeled and textured 3D art assets to visually show and document how the system works
- Created 3D rotation of a medical device to share with internal and external stakeholders

PRODUCE ASSOCIATE - FRESH MARKET/GIANT

HORSHAM, PA

NOVEMBER 2013 - JUNE 2019

- Restock produce and ensure available products are fresh daily
- Respond to shopper inquiries, assist with locating specific products and provide overall friendly customer service